mymaa.com 2011-11-13

# MAA - Apartment Communities - Privacy Policy

This Site (this “ 

_Site_

”) is owned and operated by MAA, Inc. (“ MAA”). This Privacy Statement sets forth MAA’s Privacy Policy (“ Policy”) for this Site. MAA has created this Privacy Statement in order to demonstrate and inform you of our firm commitment to privacy. The following Policy describes how we collect, protect and use information we receive from visitors to our Site. This Policy applies only to information collected through this Site and not to information collected offline or through any other websites (even if affiliated with MAA) .

## THE INFORMATION WE COLLECT AND HOW WE USE IT  

(1) Anonymous Information: “ _Anonymous Information”_ is aggregate data that web sites use to administer their sites. It may include such information as your browser type or your Internet Protocol (IP) address. MAA may from time to time retain third parties to help us collect and aggregate Site customer information.  

>      **IP Addresses**. An IP address is a unique string of numbers that is assigned to your computer by your Internet service provider. Web servers automatically identify your computer by its IP address. We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server, to administer our Site, to avoid hacking attacks on the Site’s server, and may use it to gather broad demographic information. We link IP addresses to personally identifiable information solely for the purposes of retaining electronic signatures related to our application process and for future verification in the event a visitor submits false information on a submitted application. We do not link IP addresses to personally identifiable information for any other purpose.

    **Cookie Information**. As is the case with many web sites, our Site uses a technology called "cookies", which are small data files that are downloaded onto your computer. The use of cookies is standard on the Internet. We may also contract with third party service providers who assign cookies to conduct site tracking for us. These companies use cookies solely to provide us with aggregate data about site traffic. Although most web browsers automatically accept cookies, you can change your browser to prevent cookies or notify you whenever you are sent a cookie. Even without accepting a cookie, you can still access most of the features on our Site.

    **How We Use Anonymous Information**. Anonymous Information is used internally for Site administration, troubleshooting and to help improve the quality of our web pages. We may share aggregated information, such as demographics, with our existing and prospective business partners and advertisers; however, none of the aggregated information that we share will contain personally identifiable information.

(2) Personally Identifiable Information: “ _Personally Identifiable Information_ ” is any information that personally identifies you, such as your name, email address, mailing address or your telephone number. We may ask you to provide us with Personally Identifiable Information on a voluntary basis for the following purposes:  

    **User IDs and Passwords**. To access certain features on our site, we may request that you create a login name and password (a “ _User Account_ ”). We will use this information to maintain your User Account and will employ SSL encryption technology when transmitting personally identifiable information. We may also use this information to send you announcements of new Site features, special offers and promotional materials that we think may be of interest to you.

    **Email Correspondence**. Scattered throughout the Site are links or forms that can be used to contact MAA so you can comment, make a complaint, make suggestions and ask questions. Your email address is required so that we can answer your questions, and we want your name, too, so we can address our answer in a mannerly way. MAA may put information from email on file, but does not currently share, sell, license or transmit this information with third parties without express authorization from you. MAA maintains a strict policy against selling its customer lists.

    **Newsletters and Other Communications**. We offer visitors to this Site who have a User Account the opportunity to sign up to receive newsletters or other email communications from this Site. In order to sign up for these communications, you must create a User Account and provide us your contact information, such as your name and email address. We also may offer the opportunity for you to receive mailings from our partners that we think may be of interest to you.

    **Online Transactions**. We offer visitors to this Site the opportunity to submit a rental application online. We offer residents of MAAC properties the opportunity to use various online services, including an online payment system. In order to take advantage of these services, you must provide Personally Identifiable Information. A “User Account” must be established to complete online transactions.

    **How We Use Personally Identifiable Information .** Personally Identifiable Information collected by MAA will be used for purposes including administration of the Site, for communications with visitors who submit requests for information, and to allow visitors who have created a User Account to submit an application or to use online resident services. In all cases, however, we will only use your information as permitted by law. We also may disclose Personally Identifiable Information if we are required to do so by law or we in good faith believe that such action is necessary to (a) comply with the law or with legal process, (b) protect and defend our rights and property, (c) protect against misuse or unauthorized use of the Site, or (d) protect the personal safety or property of our users or the public. Please note that we may not provide you with notice prior to disclosure in such cases.

**OPT-OUT**

If you maintain a User Account and decide that you do not wish to receive communications from MAA, you can contact us at the email or postal address provided below and indicate that you no longer want to receive information relating to this Site.  

**ACCESS AND CORRECTION**

You have a right to know about the personal information that MAA holds about you, including the right to correct, amend or delete the information that MAA has on file if it is incorrect. If you wish to exercise these rights, please contact us by email or postal mail at the addresses below.  

**SECURITY**

This Site incorporates appropriate safeguards to protect the security, integrity, completeness, accuracy and privacy of the personal information we collect. We have put in place reasonable precautions to protect information from loss, misuse and alteration, including Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and database encryption. While on a secure page, the lock icon on the bottom of Web browsers such as Mozilla Firefox and Microsoft Internet Explorer becomes locked, as opposed to unlocked, or open, when you are just “surfing”. While we use SSL encryption to protect sensitive information online, we use reasonable efforts to protect user information offline. Our security and privacy policies are periodically reviewed and enhanced as required and only authorized individuals have access to the information you provide.

The security of information communicated by or to us over the Internet is of utmost concern to us; unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. Please note that your email, like most, if not all, non-encrypted Internet communications, may be accessed and viewed by other Internet users without your knowledge and permission while in transit to us. For that reason, to protect your privacy, please do not use email to communicate information to us that you consider confidential. While we strive to protect your personal information, MAA cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us directly or through our Site, and you do so at your own risk. Once we receive your transmission, we will use reasonable efforts to ensure its security on our internal systems. Depending on the nature of the inquiry, your communication may be discarded or archived. If you wish, you may contact us instead via telephone at the numbers provided throughout our Site.

**DISCLOSURE OF CUSTOMER INFORMATION THROUGH BUSINESS TRANSFERS**

As we continue to develop our business, we may buy, merge or partner with other companies or businesses, and in so doing, acquire customer information. In such transactions, user information may be among the transferred assets. Similarly, in the unlikely event that a portion or substantially all of MAAC’s assets are sold or transferred to a third party, customer information (including your email address) would likely be one of the transferred business assets.

**OUR COMMITMENT TO CHILDREN'S PRIVACY**

Protecting the privacy of children is very important to us. The Children’s Online Privacy and Protection Act of 1998 (" 

_COPPA_

") defines a "Child" as anyone under the age of 13. MAA strictly adheres to COPPA. For that reason, we do not collect or maintain information obtained through our Site from those we actually know are under 13, and no part of our Site is structured to attract anyone under 13.

**EXTERNAL LINKS**

This Site may provide links and/or advertising banners for your convenience to various web sites or sponsors that we do not control. When you click on one of these links, you will be transferred out of our Site and connected to the web site of the organization or company whose link you selected. We are not responsible for the nature, quality or accuracy of the content or opinions expressed in such web sites, and such web sites are not investigated, monitored or checked for quality, accuracy or completeness by MAA. Our inclusion of any linked web site on this Site does not imply or express an approval or endorsement of the linked web site by MAA, or of any of the content, opinions, products or services provided on such web sites. Even if an affiliation exists between our Site and a third-party web site, we exercise no control over linked sites. Each of these linked sites maintains its own independent privacy and data collection policies and procedures. While MAA expects its partners, advertisers and affiliates to respect the privacy of our users, MAA is not responsible for the actions of third parties. If you visit a web site that is linked to our Site, we encourage you to consult that web site’s privacy policy before providing any personal information and whenever interacting with any web site. MAAC’s Policy will not apply to any personal information that is collected on that linked web site.

   **SPECIAL NOTIFICATION FOR CALIFORNIA RESIDENTS**

Under the California Civil Code, residents of the State of California that have provided any Personally Identifiable Information to MAA have the right to request a list of all third parties to which MAA has disclosed Personally Identifiable Information during the preceding year for direct marketing purposes. Alternatively, the law provides that if MAAC has a privacy policy that gives either an opt-out or opt-in choice for the use of Personally Identifiable Information by third parties (such as advertisers or affiliated companies) for marketing purposes, MAAC may instead provide you with information on how to exercise your disclosure choice options. MAAC qualifies for the alternative option; it has established this Policy that provides you with details on how you may either opt-out or opt-in to the use of your Personally Identifiable Information by third parties for direct marketing purposes. If you are a California resident and wish to request information about how to exercise your third party disclosure choices, please send a request to the email address below and state your preference on how our response to your request should be sent.

**CONSENT AND JURISDICTION**

This Site is controlled, operated and administered entirely within the United States. By using this Site, you signify your agreement to the terms of this Policy. If you do not agree with this Policy, please do not disclose any personal information through this Site. This Policy and the use of this Site are governed by Tennessee law. Any claim related to the Site or this Policy shall be brought in a federal or state court in Memphis, Tennessee, within one (1) year after the claim arises. Users of this Site consent to the jurisdiction and venue of such courts as the most convenient and appropriate for the resolution of disputes concerning this Policy. This Policy and the notices outlined herein are not intended to and do not create any contractual or other legal rights in or on behalf of any third party.

   **MODIFICATIONS TO PRIVACY POLICY**

MAA may modify this Policy at any time, at its discretion, and modifications are effective upon being posted on this Site. You are responsible for reviewing this Policy periodically to ensure that you are aware of any changes to it.

   **ACCOUNT REVISIONS, REVOKING AND DELETING PERSONAL INFORMATION**

We welcome your questions, comments and all feedback pertaining to your privacy or any other issue with regard to this Site. At any time, you may request that we cease further use of your email address to send you communications, and direct us to delete the information you have supplied. If you send us your request by email or postal mail to the addresses below, we will make reasonable efforts to comply with your request. If you have given us information for one of the third parties we mentioned above and we have already passed it on, we cannot delete or change the information. In the event that you have given us Personally Identifiable Information in the past and then have second thoughts, you may send us an email or contact us by regular mail:

 Email:

Last Updated:  June 5, 2008
